<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<episodes>
    <episode>
        <title>The Will and the Way</title>
        <verse>Philippians 2:13</verse>
        <acknowledge>Let's be honest: it's hard to always do what's right or good. Sometimes, we lack the will to do good because of what we want to keep or control. Other times, we want to do good but don't know what steps to take.</acknowledge>
        <inspire>But Paul tells us that God works in us both to will and to do good. So not only will God give us the desire to do what is good, He will also help us to do it! What an awesome, loving Father we have!</inspire>
        <aspire>What can you trust God with today to give you both the will and the way to do good? Ask God for the help you need to do good today, whether it's the motivation, the means, or both. God can help you do it all!</aspire>
    </episode>
    <episode>
        <title>Let Your Words Reflect Your Heart</title>
        <verse>Psalm 19:14</verse>
        <acknowledge>We all struggle with the words we speak. Sometimes our words come out harsh, careless, or unkind—reflecting frustration, insecurity, or a lack of patience. We don't always think before we speak, and once words are out there, we can't take them back. The weight of knowing our words have hurt someone else can be heavy.</acknowledge>
        <inspire>But the Psalmist invites us to think of our words differently. By asking God to accept the words of our mouth and the thoughts of our hearts, we're acknowledging that our speech can be pleasing to God. God cares about what we say because He cares about who we are. When we align our words with God's character—speaking with kindness, truth, and love—we honor Him and reflect His presence in our lives.</inspire>
        <aspire>Today, pause before you speak. Take one moment to ask yourself: "Would I be proud to say this to God?" If the answer is no, choose a kinder, truer word instead. Start with just one conversation, and notice how this small shift changes not only what you say, but how you feel.</aspire>
    </episode>
</episodes>